{
    "id": "6353c8af6c5c486d90b780beb84eaf24",
    "title": "Simple Past Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I …………………………. him yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "was seeing",
                "had seen"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "50d482fc687749e9aaacaa93faa0525e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………. his letter yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "received",
                "have received",
                "was receiving"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "81f384c70fe24e2883ab5d68918232e8"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………….. school last year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will leave",
                "was leaving",
                "left"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "adc2c3f068f14f36baea440cf6cf91cb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Last night I …………………………….. sleep well.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "don't",
                "didn't",
                "hadn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e54a01d3565843c9841cea48e7ec67e3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………………. asleep while he was driving.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fell",
                "was falling",
                "had fallen"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "adf6db924e7e4ea7864a79386311896e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… a new bicycle last week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bought",
                "have bought",
                "had bought"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "094545e186cc4f4082fff53f5f79b3a4"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………………….. our breakfast half an hour ago.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "finished",
                "have finished",
                "had finished"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c7bc9da1c0eb4cd9a017db2cb77c2a4f"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I was in the US, I …………………………….. Chicago, Boston and California.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "visiting",
                "visited",
                "was visiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b0923044c83d430799f4beaff561b85d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………….. an old classmate of mine at the library.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was seeing",
                "saw",
                "had seen"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ab2409a72c13490898e6cbb7e638ff46"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………………… that she would not go.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "says",
                "said",
                "was saying"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "998198a0c63c4d3b9f11f7e40d1975bf"
        }
    ]
}